Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc three), 2005; SR-24169; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24167; SR-24168. Triple album.
          Catalog # B0005426-01; A-side Matrix # B0005426-01-LP03-A
        - Santana, Juelz - Mic check, 2005; SR-24170; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 16340-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16340-1-A1
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc one), 2005; SR-24171; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24172; SR-24173. Triple album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16440-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16440-1A
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc two), 2005; SR-24172; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24171; SR-24173. Triple album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16441-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16441-1-A
        - Santana, Juelz - What the game's been missing! (disc three), 2005; SR-24173; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24171; SR-24172. Triple album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16442-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16442-A1
        - Santana, Juelz - Oh yes (aka 'postman'); Shottas, 2005; SR-24174; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 16465-1; A-side Matrix # B0006062-11-A1
        - Santana, Juelz - Clockwork, 2006; SR-24175; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 16540-1; A-side Matrix # B0006717-11-A
        - Santana, Juelz - Down; Now what, 2003; SR-24176; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 15935-1; A-side Matrix # B0001535-11-A-1
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - Santana, Juelz - There it go (the whistle song), 2005; SR-24177; Santana, Juelz (Box 423)
          Catalog # DEFR 16366-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16366-1-2
        - Santana, Omar - Raver's damnation, 1999; SR-24178; Santana, Omar (Box 423)
          Catalog # MM 88463-1; A-side Matrix # MM-88463-1A S-41133
          Moonshine Music
          West Hollywood, California
        - Santiago, Lina - Dale que dale, 1996; SR-24179; Santiago, Lina (Box 423)
          Catalog # U8P-1053; A-side Matrix # U8P 1053 A/B
          Universal Records
        - Sarai - Pack ya bags, 2002; SR-24180; Sarai (Box 423)
          Catalog # EAS 59448; A-side Matrix # XSS-59448A-1B
        - Sarava - Sarava, 1978; SR-24181; Sarava (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24182. 2 copies.
          Catalog # YD-11455; A-side Matrix # YD11455-A
          Roadshow
        - Sarava - Sarava, 1978; SR-24182; Sarava (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24181. 2 copies.
        - Sargeant & Malone - Love message, 1980; SR-24183; Sargeant & Malone (Box 423)
          Catalog # HM-003; A-side Matrix # HM-003-A
          Halfmoon Productions
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Sash! - Mysterious times, 1998; SR-24184; Sash!; Cousins, Tina (Box 423)
          Catalog # X-IT 048; A-side Matrix # X-IT 048-A1
          X-IT Records
          Cologne, Germany
        - Sash! - Life goes on (disc one), 1998; SR-24185; Sash! (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24186. Double album.
          Catalog # X-IT LP-2; A-side Matrix # X-IT-LP2-A1
        - Sash! - Life goes on (disc two), 1998; SR-24186; Sash! (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24185. Double album.
          Catalog # X-IT LP-2; A-side Matrix # X-IT-LP2-C1
        - Sash! - It's my life (disc one), 1997; SR-24187; Sash! (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24188. Double album.
          Catalog # X-IT LP-1; A-side Matrix # XIT-LP0010A1
        - Sash! - It's my life (disc two), 1997; SR-24188; Sash! (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24187. Double album.
          Catalog # X-IT LP-1; A-side Matrix # XIT-LP0010C1
        - Sash! - Move mania, 1998; SR-24189; Sash!; Shannon (Box 423)
          Catalog # CMC 0001; A-side Matrix # CMC-0001-A
          Contagious Records
        - Sasha - Dat sexy body, 2003; SR-24190; Sasha (Box 423)
          Catalog # PROMO 88; A-side Matrix # PROMO 88 A
        - Sass - Much too much, 1982; SR-24191; Sass (Box 423)
          Catalog # TFW1001; A-side Matrix # TFW 1001 AS
          25 West Records
        - Sassa - When the time is right, 1988; SR-24192; Sassa (Box 423)
          Catalog # PRO-7216; A-side Matrix # PRO-7216-A-1
          Profile Records
        - Sasha - Coca cola shape; Dat sexy body, 2005; SR-24193; Sasha (Box 423)
          Catalog # VPRD 6428; A-side Matrix # VPRD 6428 A
        - Sasha - Dat sexy body Español, 2004; SR-24194; Sasha; Ivy Queen (Box 423)
          Catalog # VPRL 6413; A-side Matrix # VP 6413-A
        - Satin - City boys, 1983; SR-24195; Satin (Box 423)
          Catalog # SC 20; A-side Matrix # SC20A-RECUT
          Silver Cloud Records
        - Satin - City boys, 1983; SR-24196; Satin (Box 423)
        - Sauce Money - For my hustlaz, 2000; SR-24197; Sauce Money (Box 423)
          Catalog # SPRO 81344; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81344-A
          Priority Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - Saunders, Larry - Stranger, 1976; SR-24198; Saunders, Larry (Box 423)
          Catalog # SLP-100; A-side Matrix # SLP 100 A-1-1-1
          Soul International Records
          Buffalo, New York
        - Savage, Chantay - Don't let it go to your head, 1994; SR-24199; Savage, Chantay (Box 423)
          Catalog # RDAB 62907-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-62907-1-A
          RCA
        - Savage, Clayton - Satisfaction guaranteed, 1986; SR-24200; Savage, Clayton (Box 423)
          Catalog # V-56035; A-side Matrix # V-1-56035-240738-C-Z2
          Manhattan
        - Savage, Clayton - Clayton Savage, 1986; SR-24201; Savage, Clayton (Box 423)
          Catalog # ST53022; A-side Matrix # ST-1-53022-Z2
        - Savage, Clayton - Palm of her hand, 1986; SR-24202; Savage, Clayton (Box 423)
          Catalog # V-56016; A-side Matrix # V-1-56016-240736B-Z2
        - Savage Progress - My soul unwraps tonight, 1984; SR-24203; Savage Progress (Box 423)
          Catalog # TEN 16-12; A-side Matrix # TEN 1612 A-1U-1
          10 Records
        - Savon, Sam - My heart alone, 1991; SR-24204; Savon, Sam (Box 423)
          Catalog # CR-245; A-side Matrix # CR-245-A
        - Saxmachine - Love is the message, 1994; SR-24205; Saxmachine (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24206. 2 copies.
          Catalog # Y-58177; A-side Matrix # Y-58177A
          TRIBAL America
        - Saxmachine - Love is the message, 1994; SR-24206; Saxmachine (Box 423)
          In same jacket as # SR-24205. 2 copies.
        - Scaggs, Boz - Silk degrees, 1976; SR-24207; Scaggs, Boz (Box 423)
          Catalog # PC 33920; A-side Matrix # PAL 33920-1A
        - Scaggs, Boz - Silk degrees, 1976; SR-24208; Scaggs, Boz (Box 423)
          Catalog # JC 33920; A-side Matrix # PAL 33920-1AR
        - Scaggs, Boz - Hollywood, 1977; SR-24209; Scaggs, Boz (Box 423)
          Catalog # AS 426; A-side Matrix # XSS 163595 1A
        - Scanda-Lis - Most lethal female, 1995; SR-24210; Scanda-Lis (Box 423)
          Catalog # ECHO1262; A-side Matrix # ECHO 1262A
          Echo International
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Scandalous Tribe - Yes sir, I can boogie, 1990; SR-24211; Scandalous Tribe; Vamps 'N' Roses; Damon (Box 423)
          Catalog # M 547; A-side Matrix # R/S ALSDORF M 547-A
          !Hype
        - Scan X - Neurotronik, 2002; SR-24212; Scan X (Box 423)
          Catalog # F165W; A-side Matrix # B265617-01 A1
          F Communications
          Paris, France
        - Scarbury, Joey - America's greatest hero, 1981; SR-24213; Scarbury, Joey (Box 423)
          Catalog # 5E-537; A-side Matrix # 5E-537-A2-AR
          Elektra
        - Scarface - Hot club wax, 1998; SR-24214; Scarface (Box 424)
          Catalog # SPRO-13115; A-side Matrix # SPRO-13115-A
          Rap-A-Lot Records
          Houston, Texas
        - Scarface - Homies & thugs, 1998; SR-24215; Scarface; Tupac; Master P (Box 424)
          Catalog # SPRO-12797; A-side Matrix # SPRO 7087 12797-1-9 A
        - Scarface - Money and the power, 1992; SR-24216; Scarface (Box 424)
          Catalog # SPRO-6626; A-side Matrix # S-26595
        - Scarface - Only you; Flat Eric, 1999; SR-24217; Scarface (Box 424)
          Catalog # JOKER 52; A-side Matrix # JOKER 52-A
          Joker Records
          United Kingdom
        - Scarface - One; Catch up; Mo' problems, 1999; SR-24218; Scarface; Ludacris; Tela (Box 424)
          Catalog # 08724 81261 12; A-side Matrix # S-41871
        - Scarface - People don't believe, 1994; SR-24219; Scarface (Box 424)
          Catalog # SPRO-12700; A-side Matrix # SPRO-12700-A
        - Scarfo, Sam - Who want it, 2006; SR-24220; Scarfo, Sam; Banton, Buju (Box 424)
          Catalog # DEFR 16498-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16498-1-A
        - Schallbau - Waldeslust, 1998; SR-24221; Schallbau (Box 424)
          Catalog # LOC 288; A-side Matrix # LOC 288-1 A
          Logic Records
        - Schifrin, Lalo - No one home, 1979; SR-24222; Schifrin, Lalo (Box 424)
          Catalog # 4Z8-5520; A-side Matrix # 4Z8-5520-3 AC
          Tabu Records
        - Schimmel, Robert - Comes clean, 1996; SR-24223; Schimmel, Robert (Box 424)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8777; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8777-A SR-1
        - Schimmel, Robert - Crossover comedy remix sampler, 1996; SR-24224; Schimmel, Robert (Box 424)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8845; A-side Matrix # PRO-A 8845-A-SR1
        - Schizoid-Man - The Harvey Dent EP, 1996; SR-24225; Schizoid-Man (Box 424)
          Catalog # NR82T; A-side Matrix # NR82TA
          Nation Records
        - Schneider, Fred - Fred Schneider & the Shake Society, 1984; SR-24226; Schneider, Fred; Shake Society (Box 424)
          Catalog # 1-25158; A-side Matrix # 1 25158 A SR3
        - Scholar 1 - Turn up the radio; Just your brother, 1988; SR-24227; Scholar 1 (Box 424)
          Catalog # GF 12005; A-side Matrix # GF-12005 A
          G Fine Sounds
        - Scholar 1 - Turn up the radio; Just your brother, 1988; SR-24228; Scholar 1 (Box 424)
        - Scholar 1 - Turn up the radio; Just your brother, 1988; SR-24229; Scholar 1 (Box 424)
        - Schönheitsfehler - Fuck you, 2000; SR-24230; Schönheitsfehler (Box 424)
          Catalog # 561 893-1; A-side Matrix # 561893-1 A
          Motor Music
        - Schönheitsfehler - Sexdrugsandhiphop (disc one), 2000; SR-24231; Schönheitsfehler (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24232. Double album.
          Catalog # 543 639-1; A-side Matrix # 543639-1A
        - Schönheitsfehler - Sexdrugsandhiphop (disc two), 2000; SR-24232; Schönheitsfehler (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24231. Double album.
          Catalog # 543 639-1; A-side Matrix # 543639-1C
        - Schoolly D - Saturday night, 1987; SR-24233; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24234. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MELT LP2; A-side Matrix # MELTLP-2-A
          Flame Records
        - Schoolly D - Saturday night, 1987; SR-24234; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24233. 2 copies.
        - Schoolly D - No more rock n' roll, 1988; SR-24235; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24236. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1152-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1152-1-JD-A
          Jive
        - Schoolly D - No more rock n' roll, 1988; SR-24236; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24235. 2 copies.
        - Schoolly D - Schoolly D, 1986; SR-24237; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24238. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MELP LP 1; A-side Matrix # MELTLP-1-A
        - Schoolly D - Schoolly D, 1986; SR-24238; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24237. 2 copies.
        - Schooly D - Welcome to America (radio edit), 1994; SR-24239; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24240. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CAS 5687; A-side Matrix # XSS-5687-A2
          Ruffhouse Records
        - Schooly D - Welcome to America (radio edit), 1994; SR-24240; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24239. 2 copies.
        - Scholly-D - Gangster boogie (MC, MCs), 1986; SR-24241; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          Catalog # P# 1414; A-side Matrix # P-1414-A
          Place To Be Records
          Narberth, Pennsylvania
        - Schoolly D - Put your Fila's on, 1986; SR-24242; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24243. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MELT 2T; A-side Matrix # MELT-2T-A
        - Schoolly D - Put your Fila's on, 1986; SR-24243; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24242. 2 copies.
        - Schoolly D - Saturday night, 1986; SR-24244; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24245. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MELT 4T; A-side Matrix # MELT-4T-A1
        - Schoolly D - Saturday night, 1986; SR-24245; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24244. 2 copies.
        - Schoolly D - Saturday night, 1986; SR-24246; Schoolly D (Box 424)
          Catalog # SD-115; A-side Matrix # SD-115-A
          Schoolly D Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Schifrin, Lalo - Boulevard nights (original sound track), 1979; SR-24247; Schifrin, Lalo (Box 424)
          Catalog # BSK 3328; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3328
        - Science - Get your groove on, 1996; SR-24248; Science (Box 424)
          Catalog # 74535-1; A-side Matrix # PAP 74535-1-A-1A
          Nivek Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Scientists of Sound - Landmine situation, 1996; SR-24249; Scientists of Sound (Box 424)
          Catalog # DL3; A-side Matrix # DL 003-A1
          Downlow Entertainment
        - Scorcher - Wake up the party, 1989; SR-24250; Scorcher (Box 424)
          Catalog # CNT 019; A-side Matrix # CNT 019-A
          Scorcher Records
        - Scott, Andy - Kurgerrands, 1983; SR-24251; Scott, Andy (Box 424)
          Catalog # TAK 1012; A-side Matrix # TAK 1012 A-1U-1
          Statik Records
          Glasgow, United Kingdom
        - Scott, Christian - Bounce the EP, 1997; SR-24252; Scott, Christian (Box 424)
          Catalog # CR-403; A-side Matrix # CR403A
          Cutting Traxx
        - Scott Grooves - Mothership reconnection, 1998; SR-24253; Scott Grooves; Parliament; Funkadelic (Box 424)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # SOMA 71 R A1
          Soma Quality Recordings
        - Scott, J - One day, 2001; SR-24254; Scott, J (Box 424)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # CAT12-101 A
          Catalyst Entertainment
        - Scott, Jill - Love rain, 2000; SR-24255; Scott, Jill (Box 424)
          Catalog # EAS 14032; A-side Matrix # XSS-14032-A-1B
          Hidden Beach Recordings
        - Scott, Jill - Gettin' in the way, 2000; SR-24256; Scott, Jill (Box 424)
          Catalog # 669642 6; A-side Matrix # 6696426000 1A1
        - Scott, Jill - Who is Jill Scott? - Words and sounds volume 1 (disc one), 2000; SR-24257; Scott, Jill (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24258. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 62137; A-side Matrix # AL-61605-1A
        - Scott, Jill - Who is Jill Scott? - Words and sounds volume 1 (disc two), 2000; SR-24258; Scott, Jill (Box 424)
          In same jacket as # SR-24257. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 62137; A-side Matrix # AL-61605-1B
        - Scott K - I love music, 2006; SR-24259; Scott K (Box 424)
          Catalog # BOXMUSIC 001; A-side Matrix # BOX-001-A
          BOXMUSIC
        - Scott, Kimberly - Tuck me in, 1997; SR-24260; Scott, Kimberly (Box 424)
          Catalog # 44 78685; A-side Matrix # XSS-78685A-1B
        - Scott, Millie - It's my life, 1988; SR-24261; Scott, Millie (Box 424)
          Catalog # DMD 1177; A-side Matrix # STDM-54971-55176-1
        - Scott, Millie - Ev'ry little bit, 1987; SR-24262; Scott, Millie (Box 424)
          Catalog # PRO-432; A-side Matrix # PRO-432-A
          4th & Broadway
        - Scott, Rena - Super lover, 1979; SR-24263; Scott, Rena (Box 424)
          Catalog # DSC 133; A-side Matrix # DSC 133 SA-2 CTH
          Buddah Records
        - Scott, Tom - Flashpoint, 1988; SR-24264; Scott, Tom (Box 424)
          Catalog # GR-9571; A-side Matrix # GR 9571 A DMM
          GRP Records
        - Scott, Toni - That's how I'm living, 1989; SR-24265; Scott, Toni (Box 424)
          Catalog # NP50098; A-side Matrix # NP-50098 A
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Secrets, 1978; SR-24266; Scott-Heron, Gil; Jackson, Brian (Box 424)
          Catalog # AB 4189; A-side Matrix # AB 4189 SA
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Pieces of a man, 2000; SR-24267; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 424)
          Catalog # FDS 10143; A-side Matrix # 3972 FDS10143-1 (A) S 42583
          Flying Dutchman
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - From South Africa to South Carolina, 1975; SR-25301; Scott-Heron, Gil; Gil Scott-Heron & Brian Jackson; Jackson, Brian (Box 425)
          Catalog # AL 4044; A-side Matrix # AL-4044-SA FW CS
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - The mind of Gil Scott-Heron, 1978; SR-25302; Scott-Heron, Gil; Jackson, Brian (Box 425)
          Catalog # AL 8301; A-side Matrix # AB 4197-SA
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - It's your world (Disc one), 1998; SR-25303; Scott-Heron, Gil; Gil Scott-Heron & Brian Jackson; Jackson, Brian (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25304. Double album.
          Catalog # TVT 4370; A-side Matrix # 3972-TVT 4370-1 (A) S-51234
          Rumal-Gia Records
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - It's your world (Disc two), 1998; SR-25304; Scott-Heron, Gil; Gil Scott-Heron & Brian Jackson; Jackson, Brian (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25303. Double album.
          Catalog # TVT 4370; A-side Matrix # 3972-TVT 4370-1 (C) S-51236
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Free will, 1972; SR-25305; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 425)
          Catalog # FDS 10153 A; A-side Matrix # DRL-1-2040 A S-39139
        - Scotti, Oskar - Conscience of man, 1983; SR-25306; Scotti, Oskar (Box 425)
          Catalog # OS-1801; A-side Matrix # OS-1801-A F-1
          Vizion Records
        - Scratch-D vs. H-Bomb - The red pill, 2001; SR-25307; Scratch-D vs. H-Bomb (Box 425)
          Annotated. Signed by artist
          Catalog # FM006; A-side Matrix # FM-006-B
          Freakin' Music
          West Palm Beach, Florida
        - Scratchmaster Chuck T. - Love is blind, 1990; SR-25308; Scratchmaster Chuck T. (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25309. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SOH 1702/CFM; A-side Matrix # CFM/SOH 1702 A-C1 G1 T
          Creative Funk
        - Scratchmaster Chuck T. - Love is blind, 1990; SR-25309; Scratchmaster Chuck T. (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25308. 2 copies.
        - Scratchmo - Play that thing, 1988; SR-25310; Scratchmo (Box 425)
          Catalog # 12 BRW 91; A-side Matrix # 12 BRW 91 A//1 420E X
        - Scratchy Muffin - Got beef E.P., 1996; SR-25311; Scratchy Muffin (Box 425)
          Catalog # skint 18; A-side Matrix # SKINT 18 A1 WHITEHAWKS UP, BUT KEMPTOWNS NEVER DOWN!
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Screamin' Rachael - Love you tonight, 1998; SR-25312; Screamin' Rachael; Farley Jackmaster Funk (Box 425)
          Catalog # 3036626; A-side Matrix # DFI 98-5 303662 6 A
          Mirakkle Records
        - Screamin' Rachael - Fun with bad boys, 1987; SR-25313; Screamin' Rachael; Farley Jackmaster Funk (Box 425)
          Catalog # GG-HH-711; A-side Matrix # GG-HH-711-A
          Grand Hip-House Groove
          Bronx, New York
        - Screamin' Rachael - Fantasy, 2000; SR-25314; Screamin' Rachael; Z-Factor (Box 425)
          Catalog # TX 426; A-side Matrix # TX-426-A
          Trax Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Screamin' Rachael - I'm into you, 2002; SR-25315; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # TX 473; A-side Matrix # TX-473-A
        - Screamin' Rachael - The real thing (ode to Prince Teddy), 1994; SR-25316; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # EB 39; A-side Matrix # EB 39 A
          Eightball Records
        - Screamin' Rachael - My main man, 1985; SR-25317; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # TX110; A-side Matrix # TX 110 A PRL 86002A S Creamin #1
        - Screamin' Rachael - Fantasy, 2000; SR-25318; Screamin' Rachael; Z-Factor (Box 425)
        - Screamin' Rachael - Rock me, 1990; SR-25319; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # BBWR 112; A-side Matrix # BBWR 112-A C1 G1
          Westbrook Records
        - Screamin' Rachael - Don't make me lonely, 2003; SR-25320; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # CTX 486; A-side Matrix # CTX-486-A RE1
        - Screaming Blue Messiahs - I wanna be a Flintstone, 1987; SR-25321; Screaming Blue Messiahs (Box 425)
          Catalog # ED 5262; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-52 62-A-1
        - Screamin' Rachael - Do you want to have a good time; I need love, 1991; SR-25322; Screamin' Rachael (Box 425)
          Catalog # CB-6005; A-side Matrix # CB-6005-A DCHARLES
          Code Blue Records
        - Screaming Trees - Asylum, 1987; SR-25323; Screaming Trees (Box 425)
          Catalog # 12NTV 24; A-side Matrix # 12NTV 24 A1 MPO THANKS WAKKOS
          Native Records
          Doncaster, United Kingdom
        - Screaming Trees - Beaten by the ugly stick, 1986; SR-25324; Screaming Trees (Box 425)
          Catalog # 12NTV 10; A-side Matrix # 12NTV 10 A1 MPO THREE DOWN, TWO AROUND
        - Screwball - F. A. Y. B. A. N.; Seen it all, 1999; SR-25325; Screwball (Box 425)
          Catalog # TB363; A-side Matrix # TB-363-A
        - Screwball - H-O-S-T-Y-L-E, 1999; SR-25326; Screwball (Box 425)
          Catalog # TB2020; A-side Matrix # TB2020 A AATB
        - Screwball - H-O-S-T-Y-L-E, 1999; SR-25327; Screwball (Box 425)
        - Screwball - Y2K, 2000; SR-25328; Screwball (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25329. Double album.
          Catalog # TB 1344; A-side Matrix # TB 1344-A-RE AA-BAJ
        - Screwball - Y2K, 2000; SR-25329; Screwball (Box 425)
          In same jacket as # SR-25328. Double album.
          Catalog # TB 1344; A-side Matrix # TB 1344-C-RE AA-BAJ
        - Screwball - Somebody's gotta do it; That s***, 2000; SR-25330; Screwball (Box 425)
          Catalog # TB 2085; A-side Matrix # TB 2085 A AATB
        - Scritti Politti - The "sweetest girl", 1981; SR-25331; Scritti Politti (Box 425)
          Catalog # RT 091; A-side Matrix # RTO 91-12 A1 MPO UTOPIA
          Rough Trade
        - Scritti Politti - Cupid & psyche 85, 1985; SR-25332; Scritti Politti (Box 425)
          Catalog # 1-25302; A-side Matrix # 1-25302-A-SR1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Scritti Politti - Boom! There she was, 1988; SR-25333; Scritti Politti; Roger (Box 425)
          Catalog # 0-20870; A-side Matrix # 0-20870-A-RE1-SH1 B-31457-Re1-SH1 20831 1-1
        - Scritti Politti - Boom! There she was, 1988; SR-25334; Scritti Politti; Roger (Box 425)
        - Scritti Politti - Perfect way, 1985; SR-25335; Scritti Politti (Box 425)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2357; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1-2357-SH-1 B-21729-SH1 SLM 10371 1-1
        - Scritti Politti - Wood beez; Absolute, 1984; SR-25336; Scritti Politti (Box 425)
          Catalog # 0-20225; A-side Matrix # 0-20225-A-SH2 B-19514-SH2 SLM 7053 1-1
        - Scrunter - Soca bacchanal, 1986; SR-25337; Scrunter (Box 425)
          Catalog # NC 0011; A-side Matrix # NC 0011-A
          Hibiscus Records
          Fort de France, Martinique
        - Scrunter - Soca bacchanal, 1986; SR-25338; Scrunter (Box 425)
        - Scrunter - Summer jam, 1989; SR-25339; Scrunter (Box 425)
          Catalog # CP88003; A-side Matrix # CP-003-A VP-C8
          Charlo's Productions
        - Scum-bum - Ora et labora, 1997; SR-25340; Scum-bum (Box 425)
          Catalog # prg 7095; A-side Matrix # PRG 7095 A
          PRG (Progressive Motion Records)
          Italy